export const o_level_quiz_en_part_1 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which is not a valid Background property of CSS?",
    options: [
      "background-image",
      "background-position",
      "background-color",
      "background-iterate",
    ],
    answer: "background-iterate",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not true about W3.CSS?",
    options: [
      "W3.CSS is the latest CSS.",
      "It is smaller and faster than other CSS frameworks.",
      "It is built-in with CSS.",
      "W3.CSS is not the standard CSS.",
    ],
    answer: "W3.CSS is not the standard CSS.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which property helps to indent the first line of text?",
    options: ["word-break", "text-indent", "text-spacing", "word-wrap"],
    answer: "text-indent",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which is NOT a valid HTML event?",
    options: ["unload", "formchange", "canplaythrough", "canplay"],
    answer: "unload",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which border class is NOT provided by W3.CSS?",
    options: ["w3-bottombar", "w3-topbar", "w3-leftbar", "w3-border-gutter"],
    answer: "w3-border-gutter",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which input type is newly added in HTML5?",
    options: ["email", "text", "read only", "hidden"],
    answer: "email",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which HTML5 element represents independent content?",
    options: ["Aside", "Source", "Article", "Meter"],
    answer: "Article",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which statement about Hypertext is correct?",
    options: [
      "Plain text",
      "Text which contains pictures and graphics",
      "Text which contains links to other texts",
      "Text which describes the text",
    ],
    answer: "Text which contains links to other texts",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which operator checks both equality and type?",
    options: ["=", "===", "==", "!=="],
    answer: "===",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which is NOT correct about AngularJS?",
    options: [
      "JavaScript, HTML, and CSS-based framework",
      "It is open-source",
      "It is a framework written in C",
      "It is maintained by Google",
    ],
    answer: "It is a framework written in C",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Which table class is NOT provided by W3.CSS?",
    options: ["w3-bordered", "w3-stripe", "w3-responsive", "w3-table"],
    answer: "w3-stripe",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Notepad++ converter includes:",
    options: [
      "ASCII to HEX",
      "Binary to ASCII",
      "HEX to ASCII",
      "Both (A) and (C)",
    ],
    answer: "Both (A) and (C)",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Which operator is used for exponentiation in JavaScript?",
    options: ["^^", "//", "**", "exp"],
    answer: "**",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which element defines navigation links?",
    options: ["header", "nav", "section", "aside"],
    answer: "nav",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "File protocol is used for:",
    options: [
      "Sending message between computer and network",
      "Receiving messages between computer and network",
      "Both A and B",
      "Transfer of computer files from a server to a client",
    ],
    answer: "Transfer of computer files from a server to a client",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question:
      "Which generic inline element provides no visual change but holds content? ",
    options: ["div", "span", "label", "cite"],
    answer: "span",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "Which is a feature of photo editing software?",
    options: [
      "Red-eye removal",
      "Color and exposure correction",
      "Removing blemishes and marks",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Which filter mimics the effect of colored camera filters?",
    options: ["Gaussian Blur", "Photo Filter", "Exposure", "Vibrance"],
    answer: "Photo Filter",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "Which is NOT true about the label tag?",
    options: [
      "For attribute should be the same as ID",
      "Label can wrap input element",
      "Clicking on label focuses input",
      "All the above",
    ],
    answer: "All the above",
  },
];

export const o_level_quiz_en_part_2 = [
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Body of stylesheet consists of:",
    options: [
      "Style rules",
      "Selector and declaration",
      "Predefined classes",
      "Formatting instructions",
    ],
    answer: "Style rules",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "SGML stands for:",
    options: [
      "Standard graphical markup language",
      "Streamlined generalized markup language",
      "Standard generalized markup language",
      "Simplified graphical markup language",
    ],
    answer: "Standard generalized markup language",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "Rectangular marquee tool is used for:",
    options: [
      "Drawing rectangle",
      "Cropping image",
      "Selecting portion inside image",
      "Red eye removal",
    ],
    answer: "Selecting portion inside image",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question:
      "Which one is an online tool that uses other search engines’ data?",
    options: [
      "Search Engine",
      "Meta Search Engine",
      "File Transfer Tool",
      "Online Software",
    ],
    answer: "Meta Search Engine",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "Negative values are allowed in padding?",
    options: ["Yes", "No", "Sometimes", "Only with %"],
    answer: "No",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "Pseudo-class used when pointer is over an element:",
    options: [":focus", ":active", ":hover", ":first-child"],
    answer: ":hover",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "Which is NOT an encryption algorithm in Notepad++?",
    options: ["Hex", "Base64", "MD6", "MD5"],
    answer: "MD6",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "Which is a benefit of photo editing for business?",
    options: [
      "Enhance customer engagement",
      "Make products & services attractive",
      "Improve brand image",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "Which is NOT true about Responsive Tables in W3.CSS?",
    options: [
      "w3-responsive class makes tables responsive",
      "w3-responsive class embeds table in scrolling div",
      "w3-table class creates responsive table",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "w3-table class creates responsive table",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "Tones are created when:",
    options: [
      "Gray is added to a color",
      "White is added to a color",
      "Black is added to a color",
      "Blue is added to a color",
    ],
    answer: "Gray is added to a color",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "Which is correct based on CSS attribute property?",
    options: ["Var", "Atr", "None of these", "Attribute"],
    answer: "None of these",
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: "Identify the basic lists in W3.css.",
    options: ["w3-ol", "w3-border", "w3-center", "None"],
    correctAnswer: "w3-ol",
  },

  {
    id: 32,
    question: "Identify the WRONG statements about “Cookies”.",
    options: [
      "Cookies are programs that run in the background",
      "Cookies may violate privacy of users",
      "Cookies help track users (shopping cart, ads, etc.)",
      "Cookies cannot store more than 4 KB",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cookies are programs that run in the background",
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "Which is true about <iframe> tag ?",
    options: [
      "It’s an inline frame",
      "Embeds another document inside the current HTML document",
      "None",
      "Both (A) and (B)",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Both (A) and (B)",
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "What is NOT correct about the Style class ?",
    options: [
      "Applies only to specific element types",
      "Can be applied to any element",
      "Style-class declarations start with an underscore",
      "Style-class declarations start with a period",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Style-class declarations start with an underscore",
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "Identify the default font used in W3.Font.",
    options: ["Times New Roman", "Arial", "Verdana", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "Verdana",
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "An element can be accessed in JavaScript using :",
    options: [
      "getElementsByName",
      "getElementsById",
      "getElementsByClassName",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "________ binds the value of HTML controls to application data.",
    options: ["ng-app", "ng-init", "ng-model", "ng-controller"],
    answer: "ng-model",
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question:
      "Which is not a valid encoding standard not present in Notepad++ ?",
    options: ["ANSI", "UTF-8", "UTF-8 BOM", "UTF-16"],
    answer: "None (All are valid)",
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "Directive to initialize Angular JS application :",
    options: ["ng-app", "ng-init", "ng-model", "none of the above"],
    answer: "ng-app",
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question:
      "Browsers will usually underline inserted text in the tag __________.",
    options: ["<i>", "<ins>", "<u>", "<em>"],
    answer: "<ins>",
  },
];

export const o_level_quiz_en_part_3 = [
  {
    id: 41,
    question: "Identify the invalid image filter.",
    options: ["Motion Blur", "Plastic Wrap", "Liquify", "Solidify"],
    answer: "Solidify",
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: "<del> element defines deleted text. Browser displays them as :",
    options: ["Red color", "Strikethrough", "Bold", "Black color"],
    answer: "Strikethrough",
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: "w3-container class adds padding :",
    options: [
      "16px left only",
      "32px left and right",
      "16px left and right",
      "32px right only",
    ],
    answer: "16px left and right",
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: "Shortcut key for rotating canvas 90° clockwise :",
    options: [
      "CTRL+Shift+0",
      "CTRL+Alt+Shift+0",
      "CTRL+Alt+Shift+F10",
      "CTRL+Alt+Shift+10",
    ],
    answer: "CTRL+Alt+Shift+F10",
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question: "What is the task of DNS Server?",
    options: [
      "Translating domain names into IP address",
      "Translating into UDP address",
      "Translating into TCP address",
      "Translating into FTP address",
    ],
    answer: "Translating domain names into IP address",
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question: "Which is not a main built-in search mechanism?",
    options: [
      "dialog-based",
      "dialog-free",
      "Incremental Search",
      "Decremental Search",
    ],
    answer: "Decremental Search",
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question: "Autofocus attribute can be used on which element?",
    options: ["Button", "Input", "Select", "All the above"],
    answer: "All the above",
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: "Identify where a <section> element can be used.",
    options: ["Chapters", "Introduction", "News Item", "All the above"],
    answer: "All the above",
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "How to specify items in an ordered list?",
    options: ["LI", "UL", "OI", "None"],
    answer: "LI",
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "Which is not a valid CSS type?",
    options: ["Inline", "External", "Outline", "Embedded"],
    answer: "Outline",
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    question: "Service that helps host a website on web server:",
    options: ["Web Service", "Web Hosting", "Web Marketing", "Web Publishing"],
    answer: "Web Hosting",
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    question: "Which is not a vibrant color?",
    options: ["Red", "Orange", "White", "Purple"],
    answer: "White",
  },
  {
    id: 53,
    question: "Identify incorrect W3.Image class:",
    options: ["w3-round", "w3-circle", "w3-border", "w3-oval"],
    answer: "w3-oval",
  },
  {
    id: 54,
    question: "To cluster elements together for formatting use :",
    options: ["tag", "class", "id", "div"],
    answer: "class",
  },
  {
    id: 55,
    question: "Identify correct statement for Absolute Positioning:",
    options: [
      "Browser determined",
      "uses position property for absolute",
      "gives author control",
      "None",
    ],
    answer: "gives author control",
  },
  {
    id: 56,
    question: "How many columns in responsive grid?",
    options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"],
    answer: "12",
  },
  {
    id: 57,
    question: "Role of JavaScript in web design:",
    options: ["define content", "specify layout", "program behavior", "none"],
    answer: "program behavior",
  },
  {
    id: 58,
    question: "Which is NOT a meta search engine?",
    options: ["Yahoo", "Startpage", "Excite", "DuckDuckGo"],
    answer: "Yahoo",
  },
  {
    id: 59,
    question:
      "__________ are used to identify user input, user action and browser actions.",
    options: [
      "Input handler",
      "Event handler",
      "Document handler",
      "Action handler",
    ],
    answer: "Event handler",
  },
  {
    id: 60,
    question: "Quick Selection tool is used for:",
    options: ["Copy", "Paste", "Find edges and auto-stop", "None"],
    answer: "Find edges and auto-stop",
  },
];

export const o_level_quiz_en_part_4 = [
  {
    id: 61,
    question: "What is true about CSS Box Model?",
    options: [
      "Virtual box around elements",
      "Surrounded by padding only",
      "Surrounded by border only",
      "Surrounded by margin only",
    ],
    answer: "Virtual box around elements",
  },
  {
    id: 62,
    question: "Incorrect media type in CSS2:",
    options: ["Handheld", "Braille", "Arial", "Print"],
    answer: "Arial",
  },
  {
    id: 63,
    question: "w3-color and w3-text-color can color :",
    options: [
      "any HTML element",
      "heading only",
      "paragraph only",
      "table only",
    ],
    answer: "any HTML element",
  },
  {
    id: 64,
    question: "Shortcut key for Gaussian Blur:",
    options: [
      "CTRL+Alt+Shift+G",
      "CTRL+Alt+G",
      "CTRL+Shift+G",
      "CTRL+Alt+Shift+0",
    ],
    answer: "CTRL+Alt+Shift+G",
  },
  {
    id: 65,
    question: "Which is NOT true about External Stylesheet?",
    options: [
      "Separate CSS file",
      "Content and style in one file",
      "Content & style separate",
      "Helps parallel work",
    ],
    answer: "Content and style in one file",
  },
  {
    id: 66,
    question: "Invalid statement about AngularJS Expressions:",
    options: [
      "{{expression}}",
      'ng-bind="expression"',
      "return result where written",
      "Angular expressions are different from JS expressions",
    ],
    answer: "Angular expressions are different from JS expressions",
  },
  {
    id: 67,
    question: "________ tag embeds CSS in a webpage.",
    options: ["<html>", "<style>", "<css>", "<xml>"],
    answer: "<style>",
  },
  {
    id: 68,
    question: "What is NOT true about ng-repeat directive in AngularJS?",
    options: [
      "repeats an HTML element",
      "clones HTML elements once for each item in a collection",
      "used on an array of objects",
      "defines initial values for an Angular JS application",
    ],
    answer: "defines initial values for an Angular JS application",
  },
  {
    id: 69,
    question:
      "Which operator is used to get datatype of a variable in JavaScript?",
    options: ["instanceof", "gettype", "typeof", "none of the above"],
    answer: "typeof",
  },
  {
    id: 70,
    question: "MIME stands for ________.",
    options: [
      "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions",
      "Multipurpose Instant Mail Extensions",
      "Multipurpose Internet Message Extensions",
      "Multipurpose Instant Message Exchange",
    ],
    answer: "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions",
  },
  {
    id: 71,
    question: "Shortcut keys to hide lines in Notepad++ :",
    options: ["Alt+H", "Shift+H", "CTRL+H", "None of the above"],
    answer: "CTRL+H",
  },
  {
    id: 72,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a type of screen frames in HTML?",
    options: ["iframe", "uframe", "noframe", "frameset"],
    answer: "uframe",
  },
  {
    id: 73,
    question: "Lasso tool is best used for :",
    options: [
      "Cleaning up a selection that you started with another tool",
      "Deselecting the selection already done",
      "Remove a selection",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Cleaning up a selection that you started with another tool",
  },
  {
    id: 74,
    question: "Which directive is used to start an AngularJS application?",
    options: ["ng-repeat", "ng-init", "ng-app", "ng-model"],
    answer: "ng-app",
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    question: "_________ makes the text bold.",
    options: [
      "font-length: bold",
      "font-weight: bold",
      "font-style: bold",
      "text-align: bold",
    ],
    answer: "font-weight: bold",
  },
  {
    id: 76,
    question:
      "The most important <head> element of a webpage is a container for :",
    options: ["Links", "Webpages", "Metadata", "Pictures"],
    answer: "Metadata",
  },
  {
    id: 77,
    question: "Identify the browser which can render HTML5 tags.",
    options: ["Safari", "Chrome", "Edge", "All the above"],
    answer: "All the above",
  },
  {
    id: 78,
    question: "Which statement is NOT true for the headings in W3.Font?",
    options: [
      "Segoe UI is the default font for headings",
      "Segoe UI has more narrow letter spacing",
      "Headings allow a lesser number of letters",
      "Smallest heading tag is <h6>",
    ],
    answer: "Smallest heading tag is <h6>",
  },
  {
    id: 79,
    question: "What is NOT correct about Embedded Style Sheets?",
    options: [
      "Can embed CSS in XHTML head",
      "Can use class selectors",
      "style type attribute specifies MIME",
      "All statements are correct",
    ],
    answer: "All statements are correct",
  },
  {
    id: 80,
    question: "Which statements are correct regarding w3-panel?",
    options: [
      "for notes",
      "for quotes",
      "for alerts",
      "all statements are correct",
    ],
    answer: "all statements are correct",
  },
];

export const o_level_quiz_en_part_5 = [
  {
    id: 81,
    question: "Identify the incorrect statement about a PseudoClass in CSS.",
    options: [
      "It is a style class defined in CSS",
      "Gives access to content not declared",
      "Pseudoclass is separated by an underscore",
      "Pseudoclass uses colon",
    ],
    answer: "Pseudoclass is separated by an underscore",
  },
  {
    id: 82,
    question: "Color enhancement refers to ___________.",
    options: [
      "Enhance only foreground",
      "Enhances diamond color",
      "Enhance only background",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Enhances diamond color",
  },
  {
    id: 83,
    question:
      "Which keyword is a must to use when JavaScript code is to run in older browsers?",
    options: ["var", "let", "const", "none"],
    answer: "var",
  },
  {
    id: 84,
    question: "Which CSS specification was first declared W3C Recommendation?",
    options: ["CSS2", "CSS0", "CSS1", "CSS2.1"],
    answer: "CSS1",
  },
  {
    id: 85,
    question: "Variables in JavaScript cannot be declared using :",
    options: ["var", "let", "nothing", "set"],
    answer: "nothing",
  },
  {
    id: 86,
    question: "Which class property makes an image transparent?",
    options: ["w3-opacity", "w3-trans", "w3-grayscale", "None"],
    answer: "w3-opacity",
  },
  {
    id: 87,
    question: "An index page is __________.",
    options: [
      "index of encyclopedia articles",
      "where all internet data is stored",
      "required for internet access",
      "first page of a website",
    ],
    answer: "first page of a website",
  },
  {
    id: 88,
    question: "What does the .edu domain represent?",
    options: ["Education domain", "Commercial", "E-learning", "Entertainment"],
    answer: "Education domain",
  },
  {
    id: 89,
    question: "Which is NOT a valid list type in W3.List?",
    options: ["Small", "XSmall", "Large", "XLarge"],
    answer: "XLarge",
  },
  {
    id: 90,
    question: 'Identify the invalid <input type=""> value.',
    options: ["radiobox", "checkbox", "submit", "text"],
    answer: "radiobox",
  },
  {
    id: 91,
    question:
      "Which JavaScript statement is used to perform different actions based on different conditions?",
    options: ["if", "for", "while", "switch"],
    answer: "switch",
  },
  {
    id: 92,
    question:
      "Which of the following can be used as prefix for AngularJS directives?",
    options: ["data", "ng", "both A & B", "none"],
    answer: "both A & B",
  },
  {
    id: 93,
    question: "JavaScript can change :",
    options: [
      "HTML Content",
      "HTML Attribute Values",
      "HTML Styles",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    answer: "All of the above",
  },

  {
    id: 94,
    question:
      "What protocol is used by all computer connections to the Internet ?",
    options: ["UDP", "FTP", "TCP/IP", "Telnet"],
    correctAnswer: "TCP/IP",
  },
  {
    id: 95,
    question:
      "__________ is used to specify a new condition to test if the first condition is false.",
    options: ["if", "else", "else if", "none of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "else if",
  },
  {
    id: 96,
    question: "Identify the non-semantic elements in HTML tags.",
    options: ["<div>", "<form>", "<table>", "<article>"],
    correctAnswer: "<div>",
  },
  {
    id: 97,
    question: "Which is NOT true about CSS ?",
    options: [
      "CSS is Cascading Style Sheet",
      "Separate content from presentation",
      "Establish visual layout of a Webpage",
      "Markup the content of the webpage",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Markup the content of the webpage",
  },
  {
    id: 98,
    question: "Which is NOT a valid text alignment class in W3.Text ?",
    options: [
      "w3-left-align",
      "w3-right-align",
      "w3-center",
      "w3-center-align",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "w3-center-align",
  },
  {
    id: 99,
    question: "HTTP PUT request method is used to :",
    options: [
      "Return contents of a specified document",
      "Return header information",
      "Replace the specified document with the enclosed data",
      "Execute the specified document with the enclosed data",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Replace the specified document with the enclosed data",
  },
  {
    id: 100,
    question: "Which statement is used to come out of a switch block ?",
    options: ["exit", "break", "default", "out"],
    correctAnswer: "break",
  },
];
